

Hanen Ben Hassen UX Designer

Contact

♠ Berlin

+49(0)17621879918

benhassenhanen@gmail.com

github.com/hanen13129

in linkedin.com/in/hanenbenhassen/

Summary

A well-rounded and driven self-starter with both a strong team ethic and the ability to work independently.

A number of years' experience across Retail, Production and Supply, Construction and Financial Services.

Over the past year, I realized that I had many skills in figma and creating prototypes, so I started to focus on improving my skills in creative thinking, analytical skills, and web design.

Skills

- Teamwork skills
- Creative thinking
- Communication skills
- Time management
- Graphic design
- Problem solving skills

Education and Qualifications

Google UX Design | December - Mars 2022 Coursera - Online

Full-Stack Web Development Program | August - January 2022 CareerFoundry- Berlin

Programming with Java | September -December 2021 ReDI School-Berlin

Fundamentals of Social Media Advertising | August 2021 Coursera-Online **Social Media Management |** June 2021 Coursera-Online

Intro to Java | March 2021 _ June 2021 ReDI School-Berlin

Bachelor in Business Informatics | 2008-2012 Higher Institute of Management (ISG)-

Professional Experience

Production Manager

CRK Maroquineries, June 2013 - November 2018 | Tunis-TN

Ensure production meets legal and regulatory requirements as per industrial policy.

Tunis-TN

- Creation and management of production plan with workshop leaders.
- Supervise production services and monitor performance.
- Respond to and manage the resolution of issues and technical queries.
- Production process optimisation and proactively manage changes.
- Plan, design, test and execute production improvement projects.
- Leading and facilitating workshops.

Production Coordinator

CRK Maroquineries, july 2012 - Mai 2013 | Tunis-TN

- Schedules and coordinates flow of work between departments of manufacturing plant to expedite production
- Establishes priorities for specific customer orders, and revises schedule according to specifications, established priorities.
- Compiles reports concerning progress of work
- Use SAGE to track and locate production units.
- ❖ Develop work orders and schedules for upcoming productions.
- Work with Managers to coordinate, plan and delegate daily work responsibilities to production staff.
- Work with management in coordinating and planning journal production activities.

Banking Assistant

Attijari Bank , July 2009 | Tunis-TN

- Serving and dealing with customers requests, reviews, advisory and issue resolution
- Allocating customer requests to appropriate resolving party open accounts, new products, account review
- Explaining new products and services to the customer
- Dealing with travel money and insurances
- Ensuring that all monies are banked correctly and the station balances correctly
- Ensuring that documentation and logs are accurate

Projects

Meet App

https://github.com/hanen13129/Meet-App

Built a serverless, progressive web application with React using a test driven development technique using Google calendar API to fetch upcoming events.

Flix App

https://github.com/hanen13129/myFlix-client

application using MERN stack and React where users can view movies in a database and add favorite movies to a list in their account.

Systems, Tools and Techniques

- Ms Office
- ♦ Html / CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- **♦** Angular
- ♦ MySQL
- Photoshop CS
- **❖** Figma
 - Sage
- jQuery
- **♦** MongoDB

Languages

Arabic : native French : fluentEnglish : fluent German :B1